## Yuan-Hong Liao

CONTACT National Tsing Hua University.

Hsinchu City 30013, Taiwan

E-mail: andrewlaio11@gmail.com

Website: <a href="http://andrewliao11.github.io">http://andrewliao11.github.io</a>

**Phone:** 886935327692

**INTERESTS** 

My research focuses on combining the visual and language representation through deep learning and apply it to tasks such as question answering and captioning. Recently, I've got immersed in deep reinforcement learning and intend to apply it on some visual tasks.

**EDUCATION** 

B.S. Degree in Electrical

Sep. 2013 — Present

Engineering

National Tsing Hua University

• Advisor: Prof, Min Sun

• Academic performance: Total GPA: 4.04/4.3, Last 60 GPA: 4.06/4.3, Rank: 8/105

Extension student in international **English and Professional Programs**  Jul. 2015 — Aug. 2015

University of California, Davis

I receive the scholarship from my school to attend UC Davis extension program.

**PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE** 

Vision Science Lab, NTHU

Dev. 2015 — Present

Research Assistance

• Conduct research on computer vision and machine learning

• Proficient in image/video captioning and image/video question answering

**Industrial Technology Research** 

Mar. 2016 — Present

Institute

Research Intern

• Work in Computational Intelligence Technology Center in ITRI

Present and survey on deep reinforcement learning

• Apply deep reinforcement learning on various application

Umbo Computer Vision Inc.

Jun. 2016 — Present

CV/ML Intern

• I focus on natural language object retrieval and image captioning, guided by Prof. Tingfan Wu

**SKILLS** 

• C/C++, Python, Matlab, Java, Javascript

• Caffe, Tensorflow

Experienced in Android App

**LANGUAGE** 

• Traditional Chinese (local speaker)

• English (GEPT High Intermediate level)

REFERENCES

References available upon request.